VIRAJ DHIMMAR

Web Designer / Developer



Contact Details

info.virajdhimmar@gmail.com

(+91-91576-76506

Bilimora, Gujarat.

www.virajfolio.netlify.app

Technical Skills

- Web Designing | Figma
- Web Development | HTML, CSS, JS, React
- Graphic Designing | Photoshop, Canva
- Data Analysis | Statistics
- Video Editing | Premiere Pro

Soft Skills

- · Communication
- Co-operative
- · Decision making
- · Multi-tasking

Education Background

- The Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda Masters of Computer Application Present
- V.S.Patel Arts & Science College, Bilimora Bachelor of Science - 8 CGPA Completed in 2022
- J.J.Mehta High School, Bilimora
 HSC 84 Percentage
 Completed in 2017

Certifications

HTML - CSS - JavaScript for Web Developer

Coursera | July 2021

Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp | Dec 2022

About Me

I've Invested my 3 years in the field of creative designing so I can give something more than just an ordinary. I believe in Learn - Implement - Correct cycle. That's how my journey started as a Graphic Designer -> 2D Animator -> Web Designer -> Web Developer & journey of progress is still continue. Currently working on Analysis skill with the help of IBM Data Science course.

Professional Experience

Freelancer

Nov 2021 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Understanding requirement of clients
- Make unique strategy for each client
- · Designing of packages, labels, stationery

Amardeep Aggregates Pvt. Ltd. | Project Design Coordinator Jul 2021 - Dec 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Analyzing online presence & work space as well
- Designing aspect of products i.e. Package/Label designing
- Working on In-House branding i.e. Designing of diary, pen, calendar

Indivisual Digital Marketing | Graphic Web Designer Apr 2019 - Jul 2021

Key responsibilities:

- · Designing of social media post for clients
- Make strategies for increasing online presence
- Make videos/animation art for client

Mountain mover picture | Graphic Designer Nov 2018 - Apr 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Designing of social media post for clients
- Make videos/animation art for client

Projects

T&P Registration Website | 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Designed & Developed front-end of the website.
- Mainly used tools & technologies are Figma, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL DB, PHP.

Online Python Compiler | 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Designed & Developed front-end of the web page.
- Used tools & technologies are Figma, HTML, Bootstrap, JS, Python